Guide to the Corcoran Gallery of Art and Corcoran College of Art + Design, Corcoran Gallery of Art public programs records, circa 1995-2011 COR0003.5.RG
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
Corcoran Gallery of Art and Corcoran College of Art + Design, Corcoran Gallery of Art public programs records
1994-2011
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
Corcoran Gallery of Art
COR0003.5.RG
99 Linear Feet
The Public Programs office operated from its creation in 1994 to the dissolution of the Corcoran Gallery of Art in 2014. The Public Programs office was responsible for creating engagement and fundraising opportunities through programs open to the public and members of the Corcoran. The Public Programs office also published Night & Day, which contained a calendar of events and descriptions of upcoming programs. The records of the Public Program office include program files for specific events, press clippings, and publications and date from 1994-2011.
Conditions Governing Access
This collection is open to research.
When conducting research within The Corcoran Archives collections, pleased be advised of the following restrictions:
Records of the Board of Trustees (RG 1.0) and records of the Office of the Director (RG 2.0) are closed to research for 25 years from the date of creation.
Development records are closed to research (RG 3.2).
Access to student records is governed by the federal Family Educational Rights and Privacy Act (FERPA), which protects the privacy of student education records. Student records are closed for the lifetime of the student, and are presumed to be open 75 years after the date of record creation (RG 9.0 Series 4).
Personnel and financial records are closed for 50 years from date of record creation (RG 4.0).
Please see the Public Services and Instruction Librarian for assistance.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
The Corcoran Institution Board of Trustees donated these records to The George Washington University in 2016.
Arrangement
Organized into five series: Program files, financial records, and calendar productions; Events; Musical Event Series; Art sales and commissions; and Trips
Historical narrative
This history was prepared in 2019 by George Washington University SCRC staff with the support of the Luce Foundation.
The Public programs office was created in 1994, originally under the heading of Special Programs, renamed to Special Projects in its first year, and finally to Public Programs in 1995.
The Public Programs office focused on creating engagement and fundraising opportunities through programs open to both the public and members of the Corcoran. Programs included lectures, concerts, and plays, often drawn from the local D.C. community.
In September 1994, the department began publishing a booklet called Night & Day at the Corcoran that contained a calendar of events and descriptions of programs coming to the Corcoran. In 1995, it expanded to a full bi-monthly magazine called just Night & Day, which combined information from the Corcoran Calendar publication and program descriptions from Night & Day at the Corcoran.
Night & Day greatly increased exposure for the Corcoran, and helped raise membership numbers at a time when the Corcoran was beginning to regain its footing after a period of financial turmoil.
The Public Programs office continued to provide public programing to visitors to the Corcoran until the dissolution of the Gallery in 2014.
Scope and Contents
The records of the Public Programs office include program files for specific events, press clippings, and publications dating from 1994-2011.
Art; Artists; Museums; Washington (D.C.)
- Program files, financial records, and calendar productions, 1994-2011; Series 1
  Arrangement
  Arranged in orginal order.
  - Special Programs 2005, Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Advertising Winter 1995, Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Night Day at the Corcoran 1995, Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - General Correspondence, 1994; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Speakers: Agam, Dor, Rechter, Musicians, 1995; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Program Information 1995, Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Aesthetic Aspects of Israel Examples 1995, Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Program Information Flyers, Circa 1995; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - CGA Speakers 1994-95, 1994-1995; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - General Correspondence, 2004 October - 2005 January; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Metropolitan Washington Posters '94, 1994; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Speakers: Ivan Chermayeff, 1994; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - General Correspondence: Solinger 1994-95, 1994-1995; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Multimedia in the Real World Program Information, 1995; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Honoring Harry Callahan Program Information, 1995; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Speakers for Honoring Harry Callahan, 1994; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Voces De Exilio Program Information, 1995; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Voces De Exilio General Correspondence, 1994-1995; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Voces De Exilio Speakers, 1994-1995; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Golden Mornings Speakers, 1994-1995; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Golden Mornings General Correspondence, 1995; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Golden Mornings Program Information, 1995; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Hidden Treasures Revealed Program Information, 1995; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Hidden Treasures Revealed Speakers, 1994-1995; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Hesperus Speakers, 1994; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Hesperus Program Information, Circa 1995; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Harpist Concert General Correspondence, 1995; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - Walter Persegati, 1994; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Michelangelo's Sistine Chapel Program Information, 1995; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - The Power of Feminist Art Speakers, 1995; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - Power of Feminist Art Program Information, 1995; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - Power of Feminist General Correspondence, Circa 1995; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - Loose Papers, Circa 1995; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - An Almost Holy Picture Program Information, Circa 1995; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - Round House Theater Rehersal General Correspondence, Circa 1995; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 35)
  - Round House Theater Speakers, 1994; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 36)
  - The Splendor of Venice Random, 1995; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 37)
  - Edward Hopper Program Information, Circa 1995; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 38)
  - Hopper: A Poet's Perspective General Correspondance, Circa 1995; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 39)
  - Hopper: A Poet's Perspective Speakers, 1995; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 40)
  - Teatime Films at Corcoran Program Information, 1995; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 41)
  - Teatime Films at Corcoran General Correspondence, 1995; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 42)
  - Teatime Films at Corcoran Speakers, 1994; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 43)
  - Glamorous Residences Program Information, 1995; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 44)
  - Voces de Exilio General Correspondence, 1995; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 45)
  - Glamorous Residences Speakers, 1994; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 46)
  - Kings, Queens, Knaves Speakers, 1994-1995; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 47)
  - Chelsea + Mayfair General Correspondence, 1995; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 48)
  - Chelsea + Mayfair Program Information, 1995; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 49)
  - Pre-Valentine Romance in Salon Dore Program Information, 1994-1995; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 50)
  - Salon Dore General Correspondence, 1994; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 51)
  - Salon Dore Speakers, 1995; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 52)
  - Dreyfus Affair Program Information, 1995; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 53)
  - Dreyfus Affair General Correspondence, 1995; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 54)
  - Norman Kleeblatt Jewish Museum Speakers, 1994; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 55)
  - Eric Fischl Program Information, 1995; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 56)
  - Eric Fischl Speakers, 1994-1995; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 57)
  - an Evening with Eric Fischl General Correspondence, 1994-1995; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 57)
  - [Fund Activity Reports], 1994; Series 1 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - [Fund Activity Reports], 1994; Series 1 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - [Fund Activity Reports], 1994; Series 1 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - [Fund Activity Reports], 1994; Series 1 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Bourgeois Brunch, 1994 November 3; Series 1 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Magazine Design, 1994 November 4; Series 1 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Twilight Concerts - Paris in the Fall, 1994 November 6; Series 1 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Twilight Concert - Musique de Joyce, 1994 December 11; Series 1 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Hot Art, Fakes Cultural Patrimony, 1994 November 19; Series 1 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - A Word About Words, 1994 November 28; Series 1 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Against the Grain, 1994 December 6; Series 1 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Safri Duo, 1994 December 18; Series 1 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Magazine Design, 1994 September 16; Series 1 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Magazine Design: World of Today, Glimpse Tomorrow, 1994 September 22; Series 1 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Magazine Design, 1994 October 4; Series 1 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Magazine Design, 1994 December 1; Series 1 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - In Search of Color Everywhere, 1994 September 27; Series 1 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Twilight Concerts, 1994; Series 1 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Golden Mornings, 1994 October - 1994 December; Series 1 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Golden Mornings 10/19, 1994 October 19; Series 1 (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Golden Mornings 10/26, 1994 October 25; Series 1 (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - Golden Mornings 11/2, 1994 November 2; Series 1 (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - Golden Mornings 11/9, 1994 November 9; Series 1 (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - Architect Client 10/13, 1994 October 13; Series 1 (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - Architect Client begin 10/13, 1994 October 13; Series 1 (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - Architect Client 10/20, 1994 October 20; Series 1 (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - Architect Client 10/27, 1994 October 27; Series 1 (Box 2, Folder 27)
  - Architect Client 11/3, 1993 November 3; Series 1 (Box 2, Folder 28)
  - Magnificence of French Decorative Arts 9/29, 1994 September 29; Series 1 (Box 2, Folder 29)
  - Hillwood Tour French Decorative Arts Lecture, 1994 September 30; Series 1 (Box 2, Folder 30)
  - Live from the Met - Montparnasse, 1994 December 3; Series 1 (Box 2, Folder 31)
  - Live from the Met - Majesty Pleasure, 1994 November 5; Series 1 (Box 2, Folder 32)
  - Live from the Met - Expatriate America, 1994 October 15; Series 1 (Box 2, Folder 33)
  - Louise Bourgeois, 1994 October 11; Series 1 (Box 2, Folder 34)
  - Series Live from the Met, 1994 October - 1994 December; Series 1 (Box 2, Folder 35)
  - Final Curtain, 1994 October 18; Series 1 (Box 2, Folder 36)
  - 1994 Fall Programs, Series 1 (Box 2, Folder 37)
  - Correspondence, Circa 1994; Series 1 (Box 2, Folder 38)
  - Lockbox, Circa 1994; Series 1 (Box 2, Folder 39)
  - Registrar, Circa 1994; Series 1 (Box 2, Folder 40)
  - Catalog Inquiry Forms Labels (For Mailing), Circa 1994; Series 1 (Box 2, Folder 41)
  - Ticket, Circa 1994; Series 1 (Box 2, Folder 42)
  - Invoices (Empty), Circa 1994; Series 1 (Box 2, Folder 43)
  - Corcoran - Jamie Tusini (Empty), Circa 1994; Series 1 (Box 2, Folder 44)
  - Fundmaster Finance Reports, 1994; Series 1 (Box 2, Folder 45)
  - Program Information [Twilight Concert in the Salon Dore], 1994 November; Series 1 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - General Correspondence, 1994; Series 1 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Performers [Hesperus], 1994 November - 1994 March; Series 1 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Speakers [The Magnificence of French Decorative Arts], 1994 August; Series 1 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Program Information [The Magnificence of French Decorative Arts], 1994 September; Series 1 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - General Correspondence, 1994; Series 1 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - General Correspondence, 1994; Series 1 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Program Information [Hot Art, Fakes and Cultural Patrimony], 1994; Series 1 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Speakers [Hot Art, Fakes and Cultural Patrimony], 1994; Series 1 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Speakers [In Search of Color Everywhere], 1994 November; Series 1 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Program Information [In Search of Color Everywhere], 1994; Series 1 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - General Correspondence, 1994; Series 1 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Program Information [Live from the Met], 1994; Series 1 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Speakers [Live from the Met - Montparnasse], 1994; Series 1 (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Performers, 1994; Series 1 (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Program Information [Final Curtain], 1994; Series 1 (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - Program Information [Safri Duo], 1994; Series 1 (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - General Correspondence, 1994; Series 1 (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - Performers [Safri Duo], 1994; Series 1 (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - Speakers [Louise Bourgeois], 1994; Series 1 (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - General Correspondence, 1994; Series 1 (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - Program Information [Louise Bourgeois], 1994; Series 1 (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - [Religion in America Kits], Circa 1994; Series 1 (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - Fall 1994 Programs General Correspondence, Series 1 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Budget Info Fall 1994 Programs, Series 1 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Fall 1994 Program Notes/Inter-Departmental/Miscellaneous, Series 1 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Special Projects 1994 Fall Calendar, Series 1 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Advertising Fall 1994 Programs, Series 1 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - [Loose Program Documents], Circa 1994; Series 1 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Catalog Fall 1994 (empty), Series 1 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Program Brochure, 1994; Series 1 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Ads for Fall 1994, Series 1 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Faxes Regarding Ads Fall 1994, Series 1 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - General Correspondence, 1994; Series 1 (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Speakers [Will Hopkins], 1994; Series 1 (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Speakers [Magazine Design], 1994; Series 1 (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - Notes and General Correspondence, 1994; Series 1 (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - Program Information [Architect and the Client], 1994; Series 1 (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - Speakers [Architect Client], 1994; Series 1 (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - Program Information [Bourgeois Brunch], 1994; Series 1 (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - General Correspondence, 1994; Series 1 (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - General Correspondence, 1994; Series 1 (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - Speakers [Against the Grain], 1994; Series 1 (Box 4, Folder 20)
  - Program Information [Against the Grain], 1994; Series 1 (Box 4, Folder 21)
  - General Information for "Religion in America", 1994; Series 1 (Box 4, Folder 22)
  - Federal Judicial Center Symposium Billing Materials, 1994; Series 1 (Box 4, Folder 23)
  - Agenda/Brochure/Packets [Religion in America], 1994; Series 1 (Box 4, Folder 24)
  - Speakers/Speaches [Religion in America], 1994; Series 1 (Box 4, Folder 25)
  - Tours for "Religion in America", 1994; Series 1 (Box 4, Folder 26)
  - Speakers for "Religion in America", 1994; Series 1 (Box 4, Folder 27)
  - [Religion in America Kits], 1994; Series 1 (Box 4, Folder 28)
  - [Programs for the Friends], 1994; Series 1 (Box 4, Folder 29)
  - Speakers [Golden Mornings], 1994; Series 1 (Box 4, Folder 30)
  - Program Information [Breakfast and Lecture], 1994; Series 1 (Box 4, Folder 31)
  - Program Information [A Word about Words], 1994; Series 1 (Box 4, Folder 32)
  - Speakers [A Word about Words], 1994; Series 1 (Box 4, Folder 33)
  - General Correspondence, 1994; Series 1 (Box 4, Folder 34)
  - Public Programs FY95 Spring Ads / Brochure, 1995; Series 1 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Public Programs Fy95 Spring Misc., 1995; Series 1 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Golden Mornings Spring FY95 Exhibitions Canceled, 1995; Series 1 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Present Meets Past Collecting Amer. Art, Circa 1995; Series 1 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - FY95 01-18-95-4134 Supplementary Salaries, 1995; Series 1 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Susan Stamberg Cancelled Spring 1995, Series 1 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Death, Divorce and Dissolution, Circa 1995; Series 1 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Corcoran Night Day, 1995 May-June; Series 1 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Program Information, Circa 1995; Series 1 (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Public Programs Spring FY95 Art Politics Frank Rich, Circa 1995; Series 1 (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Public Programs Spring FY95 Leonard Bernstein, Circa 1995; Series 1 (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - Public Programs Spring FY95 Al Carmines, Circa 1995; Series 1 (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - Public Programs Spring FY95 Diplomatic Reception Rooms, Circa 1995; Series 1 (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - Public Programs Spring FY95 The Director's Eye, Circa 1995; Series 1 (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - Public Programs Spring FY95 First Lady Suite, Circa 1995; Series 1 (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - Public Programs Spring FY95 Gardening With Water, Circa 1995; Series 1 (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - Public Programs Spring FY95 Golden Mornings Series, Circa 1995; Series 1 (Box 5, Folder 17)
  - Public Programs Spring FY95 Haitain Voodoo, Circa 1995; Series 1 (Box 5, Folder 18)
  - Public Programs Spring FY95 Liturgical Music, Circa 1995; Series 1 (Box 5, Folder 19)
  - Public Programs Spring FY95 Pedro Meyer, Circa 1995; Series 1 (Box 5, Folder 20)
  - Public Programs Spring FY95 Renoir Film Series, Circa 1995; Series 1 (Box 5, Folder 21)
  - Public Programs Spring FY95 Royal But Not Regal, Circa 1995; Series 1 (Box 5, Folder 22)
  - Public Programs Spring FY95 White House - Rex Scouten, Circa 1995; Series 1 (Box 5, Folder 23)
  - Public Programs Spring FY95 Singles Series Ecuador, Circa 1995; Series 1 (Box 5, Folder 24)
  - Public Programs Spring FY95 Singles Series Argentina, Circa 1995; Series 1 (Box 5, Folder 25)
  - Public Programs Spring FY95 Singles Series Chile, Circa 1995; Series 1 (Box 5, Folder 26)
  - Public Programs Spring FY95 Turkey Seminar, Circa 1995; Series 1 (Box 5, Folder 27)
  - Public Programs Spring FY95 Virtoosa Italiana, Circa 1995; Series 1 (Box 5, Folder 28)
  - Summer FY96 Gen Info-Adv.-Bro., Circa 1995; Series 1 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - American Colonialism Sum FY 96 General Correspondence, Circa 1995; Series 1 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Final Pastorale Concert Summer FY 96, Circa 1995; Series 1 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - American Colonialism Sum FY 96 Program Information, Circa 1995; Series 1 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - American Politicians Sum Fy 96 General Correspondence, Circa 1995; Series 1 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - American Colonialism Sum FY 96 Program Information, Circa 1995; Series 1 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Austrian Series Sum FY 96 General Correspondence, Circa 1995; Series 1 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Austrian Series Sum FY 96 Program Information, Circa 1995; Series 1 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Golden Mornings Sum FY 96 General Correspondence, Circa 1995; Series 1 (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Golden Mornings Sum FY 96 Program Information, Circa 1995; Series 1 (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Arshire Gorky Sum FY 96 General Correspondence, Circa 1995; Series 1 (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - Arshire Gorky Sum FY 96 Program Information, Circa 1995; Series 1 (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - Art of Indian Cuisine Summer FY96 Program Information, Circa 1995; Series 1 (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - Art of Indian Cuisine Summer FY96 General Correspondence, Circa 1995; Series 1 (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - How To Look at art Sum FY 96 General Correspondence, Circa 1995; Series 1 (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - How to Look at Art Sum FY 96 Program Information, Circa 1995; Series 1 (Box 6, Folder 16)
  - Kennedy Film Sum FY 96 General Correspondence, Circa 1995; Series 1 (Box 6, Folder 17)
  - Kennedy Film Sum FY 96 Program Information, Circa 1995; Series 1 (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - Jump Up / Jump Start Sum FY 96 Program Information, Circa 1995; Series 1 (Box 6, Folder 19)
  - Jump Up / Jump Start Sum FY 96 General Correspondence, Circa 1995; Series 1 (Box 6, Folder 20)
  - Mondrian Lecture Sum FY 96 Program Information, Circa 1995; Series 1 (Box 6, Folder 21)
  - Mondrian Lecture Sum FY 96 General Correspondence, Circa 1995; Series 1 (Box 6, Folder 22)
  - Quintana Lecture Sum FY 96 Program Information, Circa 1995; Series 1 (Box 6, Folder 23)
  - Quintana Lecture Sum FY 96 General Correspondence, Circa 1995; Series 1 (Box 6, Folder 24)
  - James McNeill Whistler Sum FY 96 General Correspondence, Circa 1995; Series 1 (Box 6, Folder 25)
  - James McNeill Whistler Sum FY 96 Program Information, Circa 1995; Series 1 (Box 6, Folder 26)
  - Loose Papers, Circa 1995; Series 1 (Box 6, Folder 27)
  - Canceled Program Fall FY 95 Ingmar Bergman's Movie Music Live!, Circa 1995; Series 1 (Box 6, Folder 28)
  - 15c. Art and Politics Fall FY 96 General Correspondence, Circa 1995; Series 1 (Box 6, Folder 29)
  - 15c. Art and Politics Fall FY 96 Program Information, Circa 1995; Series 1 (Box 6, Folder 30)
  - Roberta Peters Concert Fall FY 96 Program Information, Circa 1995; Series 1 (Box 6, Folder 31)
  - Roberta Peters Concert Fall FY96 General Correspondence, Circa 1995; Series 1 (Box 6, Folder 32)
  - Italian Design Series Fall FY 96 General Correspondence, Circa 1995; Series 1 (Box 6, Folder 33)
  - Italian Design Series Fall FY 96 Program Information, Circa 1995; Series 1 (Box 6, Folder 34)
  - Barbaralee Interview Fall FY 96 Program Information, Circa 1995; Series 1 (Box 6, Folder 35)
  - Barbaralee Interview Fall FY 96 General Correspondence, Circa 1995; Series 1 (Box 6, Folder 36)
  - Raised by Wolves Fall FY 96 Program Information, Circa 1995; Series 1 (Box 6, Folder 37)
  - Raised by Wolves Fall FY 96 General Correspondence, Circa 1995; Series 1 (Box 6, Folder 38)
  - A New Look At Art In Public Places Fall FY 96 General Correspondence, Circa 1995; Series 1 (Box 6, Folder 39)
  - Boone Bleckner Fall FY 96 Program Information, Circa 1995; Series 1 (Box 6, Folder 40)
  - Boone Bleckner Fall FY 96 General Correspondence, Circa 1995; Series 1 (Box 6, Folder 41)
  - Eisenman Lecture Fall FY 96 General Correspondence, Circa 1995; Series 1 (Box 6, Folder 42)
  - Eisenman Lecture Fall FY 96 Program Information, Circa 1995; Series 1 (Box 6, Folder 43)
  - 5/19/96 Leontovych, Spring FY96, 1996 May 19; Series 1 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Art, Coffee, Canapes (Finish Embassy) Spring FY96, 1996 May 20; Series 1 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Graves Spring FY96, 1996 May 14; Series 1 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Collecting Photographs Spring FY96, 1996 May 23,30 - June 6,13; Series 1 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - PP196L Cezanne Preview May 29 FY1996, 1996 May 29; Series 1 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Alexander Garvin Spring FY96, 1996 June 10; Series 1 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Oval Room Spring FY96, 1996 June 1; Series 1 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Hampden-Sydney, Spring FY96, 1996 June 2; Series 1 (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Hampden-Sydney Music Festival Brochures, Circa 1995; Series 1 (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Guy Bush Spring FY96, 1996 June 3; Series 1 (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - Love Letters (Round House) Spring FY96, 1996 June 11; Series 1 (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - Vatican Museums FY96 Behind the Scenes, 1996 June 12; Series 1 (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - Jenny Lind FY96, 1996 June 18; Series 1 (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - Eakins Sprinig FY96, 1996 June 19; Series 1 (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - WPA Ceridwen Morris May-July 1996 Programming, 1996 May-July; Series 1 (Box 7, Folder 15)
  - Henri Art Auction Spring 1996 / FY96, 1996 April-June; Series 1 (Box 7, Folder 16)
  - Canceled, Circa 1995; Series 1 (Box 7, Folder 17)
  - Canceled, Circa 1995; Series 1 (Box 7, Folder 18)
  - Spring FY1996 Magazine, Series 1 (Box 7, Folder 19)
  - Spring FY1996 Gen Info - Adver., Circa 1995; Series 1 (Box 7, Folder 20)
  - Corcoran: Night Day May/June 1996, Series 1 (Box 7, Folder 21)
  - 1/8/96 Dunlap, Winter FY96, 1996 January 8; Series 1 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - 1/18/96 Artschwager, Winter FY96, 1996 January 18; Series 1 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - 1/22/96 Foreman, Winter FY96, 1996 January 22; Series 1 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - 1/29/96 Gero, Winter FY96, 1996 January 29; Series 1 (Box 8, Folder 4)